{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Wood Stairs \u0026 Railing Contractors","__cache./api/resource/task/40423/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40423,"taskName":"Wood Stairs and Railings - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Wood Stairs and Railings","xmTaskDescriptor":"Wood Stairs \u0026 Railing Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":284,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Carpenters Stairs building build Railings","textMessagingName":"Install Wood Stairs","rolloverLongDesc":"Basic stairways can be handled by any competent carpenter, but ornate \u0026 curved stairways \u0026 associated balconies are normally handled by a specialist who is sometimes called a stair-builder. Such stairways are often custom crafted for each project. Includes wooden spiral staircases.","rolloverShortDesc":"Build custom staircase or install pre-fab unit.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Wood Stairs and Railings.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Stair Railing Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace or Install Wood Stairs","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":9,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Note: If your repair is not very complex or you have a variety of small projects, you might consider ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"requesting a Handyman.","bridgeTaskLinkId":1437,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Wood Stairs \u0026 Railings Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Wood Stairs and Railings - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Wood Stairs \u0026 Railing Project","urlName":"Wood-Stairs-and-Railings-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Wood Stair \u0026 Railing Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install, Replace","searchKeywords":"Carpenters,Stairs,building,build,Railings,Wood,wooden,structural,rough,down,pull,cases,spiral,outdoor,woooden,stairway,exterior,deck,custom,carpentry","emcCategoryOid":-12010,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":715,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40423/":{"taskOID":40423,"originalTaskOID":40423,"setID":715,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4631,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Stairs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of stairs do you want installed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3318,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior covered with carpet","answerDisplayText":"Interior covered with carpet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3339,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Interior stained","answerDisplayText":"Interior stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3331,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Interior painted","answerDisplayText":"Interior painted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6136,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Straight","answerDisplayText":"Straight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1741,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Curved","answerDisplayText":"Curved","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5950,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Spiral","answerDisplayText":"Spiral","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3447,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Landing mid-stair","answerDisplayText":"Landing mid-stair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4609,"questionDisplayText":"Stair Construction","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How will the stairs be constructed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4415,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Open on one side (railing on one side, wall on the other)","answerDisplayText":"Open on one side (railing on one side, wall on the other)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4416,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Open on two sides (railings on both sides)","answerDisplayText":"Open on two sides (railings on both sides)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4414,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Open on no sides (railings on no sides, just a hand rail)","answerDisplayText":"Open on no sides (railings on no sides, just a hand rail)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4631,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Stairs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of stairs do you want installed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3318,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior covered with carpet","answerDisplayText":"Interior covered with carpet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3339,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Interior stained","answerDisplayText":"Interior stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3331,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Interior painted","answerDisplayText":"Interior painted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6136,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Straight","answerDisplayText":"Straight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1741,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Curved","answerDisplayText":"Curved","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5950,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Spiral","answerDisplayText":"Spiral","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3447,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Landing mid-stair","answerDisplayText":"Landing mid-stair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3318,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior covered with carpet","answerDisplayText":"Interior covered with carpet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3339,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Interior stained","answerDisplayText":"Interior stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3331,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Interior painted","answerDisplayText":"Interior painted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6136,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Straight","answerDisplayText":"Straight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1741,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Curved","answerDisplayText":"Curved","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5950,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Spiral","answerDisplayText":"Spiral","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3447,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Landing mid-stair","answerDisplayText":"Landing mid-stair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4609,"questionDisplayText":"Stair Construction","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How will the stairs be constructed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4415,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Open on one side (railing on one side, wall on the other)","answerDisplayText":"Open on one side (railing on one side, wall on the other)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4416,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Open on two sides (railings on both sides)","answerDisplayText":"Open on two sides (railings on both sides)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4414,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Open on no sides (railings on no sides, just a hand rail)","answerDisplayText":"Open on no sides (railings on no sides, just a hand rail)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4415,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Open on one side (railing on one side, wall on the other)","answerDisplayText":"Open on one side (railing on one side, wall on the other)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4416,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Open on two sides (railings on both sides)","answerDisplayText":"Open on two sides (railings on both sides)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4414,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Open on no sides (railings on no sides, just a hand rail)","answerDisplayText":"Open on no sides (railings on no sides, just a hand rail)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}